Practice.
Yes.
Keep your back straight.
Good.
Yes. That's my child.
Adele, let's see.
Yes, that's it.
Point your toes.
Open your arms out to second.
This arm out to second.
I need you
to stretch to the side.
You must always
stand like this, Deni.
Then you will look very nice.
Now smile a little bit.
Yes.
Yes, Betrisya. Do this.
Yes, we've got
the 3 best friends there.
Congratulations, Betrisya.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Deni.
Last but not least...
...Adele!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Yes!
This is just the beginning.
You will be getting...
...a lot more prizes, dear!
I'm so proud of you!
Police believe the extremists
are headed by professionals.
Adele.
The moment of truth.
All praises to Allah.
Adele, I'm so proud of you!
I got accepted!
–Me too!
Oh my God!
–Congratulations!
I'm really sorry that you
won't be coming with us, Deni.
Russia is so far.
We will surely miss you.
Don't worry about me.
You two are amazing.
I'm just happy knowing
that you made it.
There are many
roads to success, Deni.
You'll find it.
I know it.
Last order of the day.
I want to run another
piece on the hijab...
...but with a different
point of view.
I hear the Malay style is
being adopted all over...
...the world at the moment.
It's not exciting enough.
I want something
bigger than that.
Do you have anything?
Style!
–Style.
We have to put the Muslimah
style at the forefront.
Create an awareness.
Create?
That is a great angle for a story.
Yes!
As long as we are not telling
people to uncover their awrah...
...or wear a hijab but
still reveal their awrah.
Finally, all our
dreams have come true.
Congratulations!
–Thank you, Dad!
Come.
Let's celebrate.
No! There's no need.
We have to celebrate!
Our little girl is now...
...a superstar!
Your dreams are going
to come to fruition...
...and all of our hardwork
is finally paying off!
All the training,
costume fittings,...
...the long practice sessions
day and night,...
...the journey to and from
shows during weekends.
Thank you to those toes
that bear all the pain!
Tell me about it.
Sometimes I can tell that you...
...hide your worries.
Am I right?
I work hard because I worry!
You are clever just
like your grandmother.
Speaking of your grandmother,
tomorrow we'll go back...
...and visit her.
But now...
...we have to celebrate!
I'm too big to be carried!
But you're still my little girl!
Let's go!
–Wait for me!
Grandmother!
–Adele!
Hi!
What a surprise!
–We were in the area.
Peace be upon you, Mum.
–Peace be upon you, too.
This lovely young lady
still needs to improve...
...her recitation of the Quran.
So she needs to stay here...
...for the time being.
Until when?
I can't say.
We have come with good news, Mum.
You have good news?
You've made a decision?
I got into ballet school!
Congratulations, Adele!
Come in. You must be hungry.
You travelled a long journey.
Let's go inside.
You shouldn't live
your unmet ambitions...
...through another...
...no matter how
close she is to you.
Ballet is Adele's dream too.
It is better if she chooses
her own path in life.
We have chosen the same path, Mum.
No one forced Adele into this.
Plus, this is the role
of the parents, Mum.
To place the child in a place
where she can thrive...
...in everything she does.
Everything? There are
things that you didn't do.
I know what you mean by that.
I'm not ready for this...
...and it's not yet
the time for it!
Adele and I have a dream
that we can achieve...
...and it is
really beautiful, Mum.
You can't force me stop!
Dreams are beautiful,
but they are fragile.
What's important is that we are
obedient to the commands of Allah.
We have to keep our faith strong.
Rooted in a firm foundation.
Goodbye, Mum.
May peace be upon you.
Are you sure you want
to stay here, Adele?
Let her strengthen
her spirituality here.
Breathe in the fresh air
of the open space...
...like it is here...
...before she goes
to Russia all by herself.
She won't be going
there all by herself, Mum.
Betrisya will be with her too.
Plus, I won't let
her go to Russia all alone.
I'll be going with her.
Bye, dear.
Take good care, okay dear?
Goodbye, Mum.
Call me, all right?
–Okay.
Peace be upon you, Mum.
–Peace be upon you too.
How are we going to
learn Russian? It's so hard!
We'll manage. I'm sure
it's beautiful over there.
Cold, but beautiful.
Really cold!
Too bad Deni won't
be there to keep you warm.
Betrisya! Winter clothes
will do, okay?
I know.
You know
that you like him too.
He likes you too.
We are friends.
Friends like one another.
But this is more than that.
I'm his friend too...
...but he doesn't look at
me the way he looks at you.
You're crazy.
–You are crazy in love!
I am only crazy for Russia!
That's amazing!
Where are you practicing?
With my mum.
We are given a choice.
A choice to display virtue...
...or vice...
...if we do not restrain...
...through our actions
and the way we dress.
Hello?
Are you still there?
Yes. I'm here.
Adele, take a look at this one.
Isn't it pretty?
It's pretty.
–Try it on for me.
This is your favourite
colour, isn't it?
It's a soft colour.
It's nice!
I'll buy this one for you.
I don't know.
I'm not ready for it.
It's okay. Just take one.
Just keep it. Who knows,
one day when you are ready...
...you'll have one in hand.
Right?
Okay, just in case.
RM100.
RM50.
What will I do if I miss you?
I'll be back before
you even know it.
Russia's gain is our loss.
Promise me that you
won't forget your roots.
Even though the branches of a tree
grow in different directions,...
...the roots will still remain
where the tree was first planted.
I know where
the soil is richest.
All praises to Allah.
I love this part.
It always get me so excited.
Me too. It's a shame the
shoes don't last that long.
That's the beauty of it.
They dance together with us.
Those who watch the performance
will not forget it.
We are like Romeo
and these shoes...
...are like Juliet.
I wonder what your
first performance will be.
Swan Lake.
I love the costumes.
I want it
to be Sleeping Beauty.
It's always been my favourite.
Whatever it is,
I can't wait to watch it.
Are you going to visit us?
Of course.
Did you think it would
be that easy to escape from me?
I wonder what we would
do if we didn't dance.
I don't know.
I can't see myself doing
anything else other than dance.
You don't have anything
else to fall back on?
No.
–You don't?
A person as organised as you
would usually have a plan.
My life is empty without ballet.
Guys, wait!
Thank you.
–Thanks.
Who knows?
One day we might dance
to the great love story...
...of Adele and Deni!
No. Stories like that...
...usually have a tragic ending.
Finally you admit to it!
–I've given up trying...
...to convince you otherwise.
Great!
Now we can plan your wedding!
Have you ever thought
about wearing it?
My mum wants me to, but I told her
it's not possible in our world.
My mum and I have
never talked about it.
That means she understands
the world of ballet. You're lucky.
Your mum isn't like my mum.
But I do often talk about
it with my grandmother.
You're willing to give up your
hardwork for the hijab?
No. Of course not.
You can't let all your talent
and hardwork go to waste...
...over a piece of cloth.
It isn't just a piece of cloth.
I know, but there's no way
the world of ballet...
...will ever accept the hijab.
Adele, we're still young.
We have a long life ahead of us.
We can wear the hijab when
we're old, sitting by the lake...
...at the countryside one day.
It's just not possible
the two worlds can co–exist.
Let's go.
–All right.
I can't wait for the day I can
pull off a Grand Jete like you.
One day I will have...
...a poster of you
on my bedroom wall!
You are my inspiration, Adele.
Don't make me blush.
Only Deni can do that.
From the earth
did We create you...
...and into it
shall We return you...
...and from it shall We
bring you out once again.
In the name of Allah
and with Allah,...
...and from Allah,
and to Allah,...
...and in the name
of the religion of Rasulullah.
This is the promise of God and the
truth brought by the messengers.
It could have been me.
It's not just a hijab.
Awrah is everything we do.
It is our actions,
what we say,...
...and it is who we are.
Sometimes we forget
the awrah...
...isn't just for women.
It isn't just the hijab.
Adele?
If you're not having
dinner with me tonight,...
...are you going out with
your friends?
I don't have anyone I can call.
I know this is hard for you.
But I don't know what to do.
I'm sure that with time,
things will get back to normal.
You'll miss the train.
It's all right.
I'll take the next one.
Let's go for a drink.
It's okay.
I have a class to go to.
Sorry, Mum.
I have to go.
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4 and 5.
6, 7, 8 and 1,...
...2, 3, 4, and 5,...
...6, 7, 8.
All right. Stretch it out.
What are you doing?
I'm stretching.
Why are you wearing that?
Take it off!
You can't dance in it.
It doesn't restrict me.
–It restricts us!
Is that your dance attire?
This is my dance attire now.
You act so high and mighty.
You're no different from
the rest of us, Adele.
If you're going to be
like that, you should leave.
Get back to your positions.
You're not ready to be back here.
I am ready.
You don't need to rush into this.
This is ridiculous!
I can't practice with her...
...wearing that.
–Me neither.
Get back to your positions.
Continue stretching.
Why didn't you stand up for me?
I didn't know how to.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, Adele, but
everything they said was right.
How can you say that?
Everything that we are doing is
against what the hijab stands for!
What happened to the
girl who once said...
...that her life
is empty without ballet?
She found her roots...
...where the soil is richest.
Surely you're
not okay with this.
She will make
a mockery of this company.
Our company. Your company.
Of course not.
I will not
allow her to wear that...
...during any performance.
She is confused right now!
When it comes to the hijab,
you can't just wear it...
...on and off, as you please!
We're all going through
a hard time at the moment.
She is only making things worse.
She is always
coming in late now.
That is if she comes at all.
And now this!
–She should be expelled!
If it was anybody else, they
would have been expelled.
You know we're right.
Assalamualaikum.
Can I help you?
Maybe. Maybe not.
I'm looking for
something modest...
...but flexible for me
to move around in.
Modest but flexible
I'm a ballet dancer.
It might be hard to find,
but it's not impossible.
It's all right.
I'll help you find something.
Okay, this one is not
too tight nor too loose.
You can try it.
–Okay.
Adele, we are worried.
Where did my little girl go?
Who is this proud Muslim
woman standing before me?
I'm not a little girl anymore.
Yes, you're almost
as tall as me now.
Can we talk?
So that we can understand
what's on your mind.
It's all very clear.
What else is there to know?
Why now?
Adele, your decision is noble.
But I don't understand.
Why now?
Adele, why now?
You can't wear it,
and then take it off again...
...whenever you dance.
I don't think you're
ready for all of this.
I will not take off my hijab...
...and I will not
stop dancing ballet.
What about Russia?
Russia will get used to it.
Adele, if it's
not accepted here...
...how do you expect
Russia to accept it?
Use your common sense, Adele.
Impossible!
How are you going to dance
if you're wearing the hijab?
Yes!
That's what everyone
keeps telling me.
Adele!
–Diana!
Calm down. Let her be.
Calm down?
What are we going to do?
We don't need
to do anything right now.
I bet my mother has
something to do with this.
Adele is old enough to make
her own decisions, Diana.
Old enough?
–Yes.
She will be going
to Russia in another 3 months!
Do you think that they
will accept all this?
Maybe this is all temporary.
I don't think so.
Impossible.
If this is the case,
Russia is out of the picture!
Or maybe we just postpone
her studies there!
I don't want her
ballet career ruined!
Yes.
Yes, I am her mother.
We would like
to defer for one year.
I'm afraid that I really...
...can't allow it.
I understand.
I will be so disappointed
if I lose her.
We will not lose her.
She will come around.
I just hope
that will happen soon.
She needs to continue
training to get herself ready...
...for Russia.
I've deferred her place.
–What do you mean?
I have postponed and
discussed this with her school.
Does she know?
I'm planning
to tell her tonight...
...and I know this news
will really disappoint her.
She is a smart girl.
It's just that she can't
think clearly right now.
I think that losing someone
can make us all like that.
How could you do this?
Because this is
what's best for you.
It doesn't feel that way.
Adele Shakiri, listen
to your mother carefully.
You're not thinking straight
right now. That's why you need...
...some guidance
in matters like this!
The Quran guides me...
...and I have chosen
the path of truth.
Do you not agree with the Quran?
You don't wear the hijab...
...and you're
not dancing anymore.
So there shouldn't
be any excuse for you.
Why is that, Mum?
Adele?
Diana?
What do you want me to do?
Nothing for now.
Just let her be.
–Come and sit here.
What is happening to our family?
We can't let this go on, Diana.
I hate this feeling.
We have to accept this situation.
That's how a person who
has given up would think.
But this is what she wants, Diana!
We can't let her
ruin her future...
...just like that!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
1, 2, 3.
Soutenu.
Ibtihaj Muhammad,
30–year–old saber fencer...
...currently training
for the next Olympics.
She wears the hijab.
Amaiya Zafar.
15–year–old amateur boxer.
Currently lobbying the...
...International
Boxing Association...
...to allow her dress code
into the competition.
She's halfway there.
Zahra Lari.
21–year–old figure skater.
Almost like we do, but on ice.
Amna al Haddad.
26–year–old weightlifter.
Just because you
can't see her muscles...
...doesn't mean you
can't see her strength.
Open your eyes, everybody.
The world is slowly changing...
...and it's women
and girls like these...
...who dare to try.
They pave the way
for everyone else.
In a few years, it will
be completely normal...
...to watch a Muslim ballet!
Adele.
You can't interrupt our class.
Is that all you care about?
We are practicing!
I want to come back.
Not dressed like this.
Hi, peace be upon you.
–Peace be upon you too.
How can I help you?
–I need your help.
I was in here the other day and
I saw you assisting a young lady.
She was wearing a hijab and
she said she was a ballet dancer.
Is that right?
Ya, that's right.
What is it?
How can I help you?
She is amazing!
How can I contact her?
Do you have her address
or telephone number?
Anything that I can
contact her with?
No, actually I am
a magazine writer.
I'm planning to write an
article about her. That's all.
That's interesting.
If I'm not mistaken, she
did give her e–mail address...
...to get discount promotions.
Let me check.
All right.
Police: Extremists are
expected to attack.
Deni!
How are you?
–I am good.
Have a seat here.
Maybe I shouldn't have come.
Who says so?
You should be here.
You may be able to help us.
I don't know. I feel
like she wouldn't want...
...to talk to me.
You wait her.
Let me talk to her, okay?
Adele, open the door.
I don't want to see him.
Don't be like that.
Come out for a bit and
say hello. He's our guest.
Adele, I have never
raised you to be like this.
How are you?
I'm good.
I miss seeing that smile.
Why are you here, Deni?
I'm here to help.
How? I won't change my mind.
I know.
I'm here to help
you write a letter.
A letter?
An appeal letter to the school.
You're on my side?
Of course!
Adele, I can't
imagine you not dancing.
It doesn't matter how you dress.
Listen, Adele.
You want to pave
the way for change.
Open a new path for others.
But the responsibility
you bear is really heavy.
That's why you need me.
Thank you, Deni! You don't
know how much this means to me!
It's very inspiring
for the faith.
But would it be
inspiring for ballet?
This is something new.
After some time,
it will be forgotten.
Ballet is revealing.
Hijab is concealing.
How can one see its beauty
when everything is concealed?
The male dancers are not
allowed to touch her, right?
So how is she supposed to do
turns, lifts or promenades?
I don't agree with having
her as the principal dancer.
Farah?
She has extraordinary
talent and potential.
She's really one of the best.
But what she is doing is
against the principles...
...and the beauty of this art.
The audience needs to see
every movement and curve...
...of the limbs and
the muscles in the body.
That is the art of ballet.
That is what we do,
and that is why...
...they come to watch ballet.
When she wears a hijab, she
is no longer a ballet dancer.
In that case, we will
uphold our decision.
I don't need them.
I'm going to do this by myself.
You're soaking wet.
What are you going to do yourself?
Ballet.
I am going to do
a solo performance.
They turned me down.
I'll show them!
You won't succeed.
I am confident.
Everyone will laugh at you.
Adele.
Listen to your mother.
I will reserve 2 seats
for the both of you.
Front row.
All right.
But I'll probably be
there in half an hour.
Deni!
What is it?
–You'll see.
Open it.
You can come, right?
Say something.
I'm not sure about this.
I thought you were on my side.
I am,...
...but they'll turn against you!
I don't want
to see you end up hurt.
The person turning against me
is supposed to be supporting me.
Don't worry about me.
I'm getting used to going solo.
Don't be like that.
Hi, I am Hana,
a writer for Hijab Magazine.
We met at a boutique
the other day...
...and I heard that you were
a ballerina and wears a hijab.
Can we meet?
All praises to Allah.
Ballet is important to me.
Faith is also important to me.
I won't compromise
one for the other.
What do you want to say to those
who expect you to compromise?
Our religion gives
advice how we should dress.
But it doesn't say
that we should...
...waste our talent and ambition.
Why should I give all that up?
I just want to be...
...a good Muslim.
Your words are
an inspiration to me.
We're done.
I have everything I need.
I'm sure our readers
will love this story.
Adele, what is this?
It's my performance.
Do come if you like ballet.
I have never been
interested in ballet before.
But now, I wouldn't
want to miss this.
Thank you, Adele.
Hijabsta Ballet Girl: I want
to unite ballet and the hijab.
This is my beginning
of becoming a good Muslim.
My first ballet show
with the hijab.
It's gone viral.
Hijabsta Ballet Girl: Adele paves
the way despite challenges.
What is this?
It's very expensive.
It is out of my price range
but thank you for your help.
Peace be upon you, Adele.
You are disgracing our faith.
You are starting something...
...that will be followed
by millions of people.
Your are creating
a generation of ignorance.
You don't realise the
consequences of your actions.
Please cancel your show.
If you proceed, you will face
the consequences brought...
...upon you by the
true warriors of Allah.
If nobody takes action,
I will do it myself.
Regards, Zubir.
This hall can seat
more than 100 people.
That's a lot.
I hope they all come.
If you book this hall, we will
help promote your performance...
...at no extra cost.
This place is nice.
I'll pay the deposit first...
...and God Willing, I'll find
the money to pay for the rest.
All right.
Let me show you
the changing rooms.
We have 2. The one on the left
for women, the one on...
...the right for men.
Let's go.
Okay.
Doors closing.
You are not a true Muslim.
You are bringing down the hijab.
Wear it properly or
don't wear it at all.
Tramp.
Adele?
What is it?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Tell me the truth.
What is wrong?
I can't tell you.
You used to tell me everything.
It's nothing.
Really.
Tell me what's happening.
She is making
a mockery of our faith.
She should be raped or killed.
I want to kill this girl.
I want to meet her. I haven't
punched anyone in a long time.
I fear Allah. This is my beginning
of becoming a good Muslim.
Hello?
–Adele?
This is Farah. Listen.
I have read the article
and I've seen the comments.
Please don't go
ahead with the show.
I will not be put off
by a few troublemakers.
People who don't want
change will always oppose.
I can't accept it too...
...but I don't want
to lose you like this.
You made the decision
not stand up for me.
Forget about the hijab.
I need you.
What do I need
to do to persuade you?
Goodbye, Farah.
Thank you.
Come to my show.
All right, guys. Thank you so
much for today. See you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Miss Farah!
–Good to see you. What is it?
I need your help, Miss Farah.
Take a look at this.
She is really
going ahead with this.
I have already warned her.
So what are
we supposed to do now?
I have an idea.
Come with me.
What is it?
Death to the infidel.
All praise to Allah...
...and may peace and blessings
be upon His messenger,...
...Muhammad, his family
and his companions.
Peace be upon those
who follow His guidance.
Death be upon
those who do not.
They don't deserve to walk on
His earth, to breathe His air.
They live in sin and will
forever belong to evil.
Satan has whispered into
their hearts and possessed...
...them with his binding evil.
They are ignorant to the truth.
Disobedient to the light.
We will stop them in the name
of Allah. Allah is Great.
Adele Shakiri.
Movements tracked.
LRT Kelana Jaya Line.
5 pm. Three days time.
Her pride will
not go unpunished.
We are there, brother.
God is great.
We will stop her
in the name of God.
This isn't easy. I don't
want to get involved...
...without discussing
this with your daughter.
She has already
booked this place...
...and she has
paid for the deposit.
She is my client.
Not you.
I know. But please, Mr. Rul.
We understand your position,
but this is a unique case.
You have to help us.
Adele has been
getting threats merely...
...for promoting the show.
–That's right.
It would irresponsible...
...and dangerous if you
allow it to go ahead.
What if on the day
of the performance,...
...something bad happens?
It would give
your company a bad name.
Yes, indeed.
What do you say?
I cannot return the deposit.
That's not a problem.
Adele Shakiri.
You have rejected the truth.
Sooner or later...
...you will face your punishment.
I'm fine.
Really, Grandma.
You shouldn't have come.
But if you'll be staying
here for some time,...
...you can come and
watch my performance.
I would love for you to be there.
Adele! You've lost your mind.
That's enough.
Cancel the performance.
It's too dangerous.
You just need to rest, okay?
I need to do it, Grandma.
If not, all of this
would go to waste.
Poor Deni.
Adele.
Your safety is important.
That's enough. We won't
allow it. That is final.
Adele!
I have cancelled it.
Farah and I have taken...
...back the deposit
for the hall.
We don't want them
to go after you again.
Okay, dear?
We are now at the hospital
where Adele Shakiri...
...is receiving treatment...
...after being brutally assaulted
by Jihadi activists.
Ballerina Adele Shakiri was
brutally attacked yesterday.
She is lucky to be alive.
She was saved by a friend,...
...Danial bin Shahbudin, a fellow
dancer from her ballet school.
The police suspect this was
an attack by Jihadi extremists.
The attackers managed
to escape from security.
If you have seen
them or have...
...any information about
their whereabouts...
...please contact the nearest
police station immediately.
Adele!
Adele, can we ask you something?
Adele can you tell us
a little bit about Danial?
These people are extremists...
...and every religion
has these groups.
They do not understand
the Holy Book...
...but they make interpretations
based on their little knowledge.
They distort the meanings
of what is said in the Book.
They don't realise what
they are doing is an act...
...of violation and is against
the teachings of the religion.
They continue to preach
in the name of God.
What about the intentions of
this girl who wears the hijab...
...and dances ballet?
Even though the girl shouldn't
have been attacked...
...that way, her intentions
to dance ballet...
...while wearing the hijab
is not appropriate.
It is contradictory.
Whether it is intentional
or otherwise,...
...it is as if she is making
a mockery of our faith...
...and it is wrong.
Imagine if other people
follow in her footsteps.
What would happen then?
After this.....
–Will she agree to it?
Yes, but we have a few options.
I suggest my friend's place.
You should first ask her.
–I know, but I have...
...many friends.
–Hold on, she's here.
What's going on here?
Adele, we have discussed this...
...and  we have all agreed
that you need a break.
Get away from KL for a while.
Yes, I guess so.
I will stay with you, okay?
Yes you can, but this time...
...you will need to go
a bit further from KL.
What do you think about Perth?
Australia?
I don't understand.
I have a friend.
Her name is Laura.
She was my friend
when we were young.
You have met her several times.
Do you remember?
Yes, I remember.
–You remember?
Okay, she is now living in Perth.
She knows about what happened
to you. So I think,...
...we all think it would be
good for you to stay with her...
...for the time being until
things here settle.
Then you can come back.
If you don't like it, or you
don't feel comfortable there...
...you can come home earlier.
We are not forcing you, Adele.
It's just that for the
time being, we feel...
...it isn't safe for
you to be here right now.
Hold on. We are forcing
you a little bit.
But you can push all
that to the side, Adele.
I feel that living overseas
will be a valuable experience.
When I was younger,
I lived overseas too.
Tell Laura thank you
for her offer.
I'd love to go.
Adele.
All praises to Allah.
Take good care of yourself.
Let's go, Mum.
–Yes.
Hi!
Hi. I'm glad you're here.
Come in.
Come on, girls.
Let's show Adele inside.
They were so excited
to gain a big sister.
Do you need any help with
them while you're at work?
No, I mostly work
from home these days.
I'd like to make myself
a bit useful while I'm here.
Don't worry about that.
We didn't ask you here to work.
Besides, you'll be quite busy.
Busy?
Your mother didn't say?
That's odd.
I've arranged for you
to tutor a friend's daughter.
She's a very promising dancer but
she could use a few extra lessons.
She's coming here on Saturday.
All right.
Unless you don't want to do it.
I presumed you knew.
It's just that I've never
taught anyone before...
...but I'll give it a go.
Although I don't quite have
the right shoes with me.
I'll take you to get some.
It's very strange she didn't say.
I guess she didn't
want me to back out.
I wouldn't worry. It's just
been a tough time lately.
Yes, it has.
Dear Adele, I hope Australia
is peaceful and sunny.
I miss having
you dance with us...
...and hope that you will change
your mind. Best wishes, Farah.
Hi!
–Hi, Michelle.
Hi! It's so great to meet you.
Thank you so much for doing this.
I forgot to warn you how
much energy this one has.
Good luck!
Let's start by warming up.
–Okay.
Okay, we'll do 2 demi–plies.
Good. Open to second.
1 grand plie.
Knees over the toes.
Right.
Forward port de bras.
Recover...
...and rise.
Test your balance.
Good and second.
Can I ask?
How do you not overheat
with all that fabric on?
It's actually not
as thick as it looks...
...and it's also
designed for sports.
Oh, I see. How clever.
You know, I don't know
what all the fuss is about.
I mean, I heard
what happened to you.
I think you're super brave.
A lot of people are brave.
You're cool.
Do you want to...
...catch up for a coffee
or something some time?
Yeah, I'd like that.
–Great.
Thank you so much for today.
It was really great.
Got all your things?
–Yes.
So I'll see you again soon?
–Yeah.
It's okay. Keep going.
It's a bit chilly.
–It's okay. You'll get...
...warm soon.
–Okay.
Hold on.
Perfect.
–From the top.
Thank you!
Excellent.
Hey, my first solo show.
Yeah!
Let's go.
What do you think?
–Good.
Yeah? Hi!
Hi, girls!
–Hello.
How are you?
What's your name?
Mia.
–Hi, Mia. How are you?
I'm Michelle.
Do you do ballet?
Yeah?
Would you like to show me some?
That was beautiful!
Can you show me anything else?
That was stunning.
Do you reckon you can copy me?
Yeah? So raise your
hand up in the air...
...and in front...
...and back.
Got. Now the other side.
Cross and back.
That was beautiful. We will
do a pirouette together.
Ready? Hands up.
Terrorist!
What's wrong?
Someone just spat at me.
On the street.
–What?
He called me...
...a terrorist.
Adele!
What is wrong with people?
If only we knew
the answer to that.
I don't believe it.
You came here...
...to get away from all of this.
I'm so sorry.
I just didn't think that something
like this would happen here.
I don't know why.
The world is a dark place
for us these days.
Perhaps...
...you shouldn't wear it.
No. That is not the answer.
I've come this far.
I can't let them win.
I worry for you.
I worry for the world.
Maybe tomorrow we can work
on something more advanced.
Yeah, that'd be great.
What do you suggest?
–Maybe pirouettes?
Thank you.
–Thank you.
Yeah, that'd be great.
See you later.
–Bye!
Hey, wait! I'll walk you.
Oh, no. It's okay.
It's out of the way for you.
Are you sure?
–Yeah. I'll see you tomorrow?
Yeah, definitely.
–Okay, bye!
We don't like
terrorists around here.
Neither do I.
Let me pass.
Adele!
You can't interrupt our class.
Terrorist!
Perhaps...
...you shouldn't wear it.
I know.
I understand. It's not
what either of us wanted.
I know.
I've tried. I really have.
I'm actually
really worried about her.
She's not herself.
I can hardly blame her
with those horrible boys...
...and the things
they said and did.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, but we have
to respect her decision.
She said
she's ready to come home.
Thank you so much.
I won't forget a thing
that you taught me.
Keep in touch.
–Definitely.
Thank you.
Adele.
Mum didn't come?
Careful, Adele.
Mum!
–Adele!
Adele.
I didn't think you
would come home so early!
Where were you?
I was here.
I'm always here, dear.
I will always be by your side.
I know.
I will stop dancing ballet.
This is a gift to me.
I know that this
is a difficult choice.
The most important thing is...
...how we connect with the world.
Not just to live.
Make use of everything
you have learnt.
Take whatever is
beautiful from dance...
...and live your
life as a good Muslim.
3 months later.
Adele, can you come out
for a moment?
But I'm.....
–Hurry!
Surprise.
Come here.
Come here, Adele.
What is it?
–Here.
I love this country.
–Yes.
Yeah, it's so nice. We should
go shopping after this.
Yes.
–I have been planning...
...for the weekends.
Maybe we can explore the city.
Yeah, sure.
Hold on.
Hi, Mum!
Just arrived in Brussels.
I'm good.